Guide to the Yale Medical Library Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1954-1967; Accession 19ND-A-142
  - Iverson, K., 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Information dynamics, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - International business machines corporation, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - J, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Journal of the history of medicine (parts 1 and 2), 1951-1965 (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
  - K, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Koh, Mrs. Heseung, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Konecnik (Penn. state library), 1966 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Kilgour, F.G., classes, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Kilgour history class, 1963-1967 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Consulting, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Davenport College, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - General Kline science library, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Kline science library., cataloguing, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - YUL-mechanized card catalogue production, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Lipetz, Ben-Ami, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Yale museums, libraries and collections, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Library of Congress, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Administrative data systems, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - M, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Merriman, Dr. Henry, 1965-1967 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - M.I.T., project intrex, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Medical center computer comm., 1941-1964 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Libraries and museums committee, 1960-1966 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - MARC feasibility project, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Anglo-American conference, mech of library services, Oxford (parts 1 and 2), June 30-July 3, Oxford 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
  - Sheffield, etc..., 1966 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - New England library association regional planning comm., May 1966 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - SubbaRow library dedication, Pearl River, N.Y., April 15, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Spring joint computer conference, Boston, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Symposium, Biomath. and Computer Sci. in the life science, March 24-26, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Conference, present status and future prospects of reference/info service (parts 1 and 2), March 1966 (Box 11, Folder 9-10)